<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[5050photography]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[5050photography]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 11:40:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About the Photographer/Mission Statement]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About the Photographer/Mission Statement</h1><p>My name is Scott Cramer and 100% of the photography posted on this website were taken during my recent travels: 6 continents and 20 countries. Travel is one of the great blessings in my life and has illuminated the beauty of existence to me in so many ways: That human beings, despite our differences in appearance, beliefs, history, traditions, and values are all beautiful; sharing the same capacity for love, compassion, kindness, and peace. That the natural world, despite its propensity to rage against our existence on this planet, is unfathomable in its depth and grandeur, and deserves our utmost respect, reverence, and conservation. That the wildlife that share our planet have every right to thrive and be protected from man's destructive tendencies.  
I am convinced that spreading love and positive energy is life's great purpose. Anything you see posted can be sold (at cost to me) provided you share in this same ideal. Reward yourself by helping others, wildlife, or the environment. Obtain my artwork through donating to your favorite charity... its that simple. Each day we rise and have potential to do great and inspiring things for others. If you are inspired by my work and inspired to do awesome things for others I am stoaked to do "business" with you. 

 Initially when I started 5050photography back in 2013 my dream was to sell fine art photographic prints and split 50% of each sale with the charity of the purchasers choosing. But as time went on I realized that money has zero influence on my happiness and would be best served completely going to the charity you are passionate about supporting. So begins 5050photography's new chapter: 100% to your cause guaranteed All I need is money to cover the cost of the print and shipping... Thats the deal people. All the best to you and yours.
Scott Cramer</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/78f617b51fc21d5b8af46c104c54c6bcdd134ab8.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedabout-the-photographermission-statement/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a0b1001c-88ea-4cdd-8415-b7ee83629623</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 11:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>